

Nazar H. Blockchain Developer

Summary

I am a passionate Smart Contract / Web3 developer with previous experience in Python for the back-end and a little experience in data science.

Developed Smart Contracts, tested them, integrated them into the front-end, wrote subgraphs, implemented upgradeable Smart Contracts, Merkle trees. And made interaction scripts for several Defi projects.

I am a team player, always wanting to understand the whole architecture and participate in decision-making.

Programming Languages/Technologies:

- Solidity
- JavaScript/Typescript (Node.js)
- Python

Frameworks/Libraries

- Hardhat / Truffle
- OpenZeppelin
- Web3.js / ethers.js
- · The Graph
- Python(bumpy, pandas, sci-kit)
- · React / Vue
- Nest

Bug Tracking/Project Management Software/CVS/Build Automation

- · Git
- Jira
- Notion
- Jenkins CI / Github actions

Skills

Others:

- . Linux
- . NoSQL (Cassandra)
- . ElasticSearch + Kibana
- . Regex
- . Jupyter Notebooks
- · Agile, SCRUM
- · 00P
- · Unit Tests (mocha)

Languages

- · Ukrainian Bilingual
- · Russian Bilingual
- · English Upper-intermediate

Professional experience

MVP Social Network

Develop MVP version of social network that would be used as a browser extension and integrated into many websites.

Duration:10.2020-05.2021 (8 months)

Client: Kyiv, Ukraine

Role: Junior Python Developer

Responsibilities:

- · Develop and Architect Database Entities in Cassandra DB
- Develop Rest API and manage Web Server

Tools & Technologies:

Flask API, Numpy, Cassandra DB, CentOS Server, ElasticSearch, Kibana

Achievements: Learned about DevOps and NoSQL databases

GetU.finance Liquidity protocol

Development of Liquidity Protocol with Depositing/Borrowing functionality both from the Front-end(JS/React/Web3.js) and Smart Contracts(helped to write tests)

Duration: 05.2021-02.2022 (10 months)

Client: Ukraine

Role: Software Engineer (Javascript, Python, Solidity)

Responsibilities:

Testing and Integrating Smart Contracts into the front-end
 Developing small Smart Contract projects like MVP Oracles
 Managing and deploying applications on a Linux server

Tools & Technologies:

Web3.js, Solidity, React, Truffle, Hardhat, Node.js, Jenkins

Achievements: learned a lot about the blockchain industry and started by forking Pancake and Aave

*** over-collateralized lending platform with a stable-coin feature

Development and testing of new features for over-collateralized Liquidity Protocol with a stable-coin feature.

Duration: 02.2022-11.2022 (10 months)

Client: Switzerland

Role: Blockchain Developer (Solidity, Js/Typescript)

Responsibilities:

- Testing and Developing Smart Contracts or new featuresWriting subgraph indexing for Smart Contracts and tests
- Helping in Smart Contracts integration for front-end and back-end

Tools & Technologies:

Solidity, Ethers.js, Hardhat, Openzeppelin, Node.js + Typescript, Nest, The Graph, React **Achievements:** Increased expertise in Solidity and blockchain domain. Wrote a lot of tests, learned basic security in Smart Contracts, Merkle trees, Upgradeable Smart Contracts, The Graph, started using typescript, and now have basic experience with Nest (didn't have Node.js **back-end** experience previously)

Education

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic
Institute Faculty of Applied
Mathematics, Specialisation in Data
Science and Mathematical Modelling
(bachelor)

+ Currently studying for a master's degree there (Data Science)